[Kill Lu Ye]
What are you doing here?
Same as you.
Smith doesn't trust your Shisha Gang.
So he sent the Qingtian Gang too.
Let's go.
Young Master Lu.
Are we close?
Are we not?
I thought we were quite close.
After you, then.
[Eclipse in the Lost City] [Episode 10]
Guess why Smith sent me here.
It's nothing, really.
I just told him some
little stories about your Shisha Gang.
For example,
a sheriff defected
and became the second-in-command,
making others unhappy
and causing trouble everywhere.
Or, for example,
this former sheriff had also been injured,
with two of his ribs just broken.
Smith thought the Shisha Gang
is unreliable,
so he called me.
Why do you have to interfere?
To make money.
But more important than making money,
I want to make you miserable.
Young Master Lu,
you are really boring.
I can't compare to you.
Recovering from an injury must be boring.
Draw a card.
You are really no fun.
It seems it still hurts a bit.
[Kill Lu Ye]
What are you doing?
I should be asking you this.
You're allowed to kill me,
but I can't strike first?
Are you trying to attract
everyone in this carriage by shooting now?
So what?
This is not Ningcheng.
Right.
So no one will collect your corpse.
There's no bullets.
Fooled you.
Have you figured out how to kill me?
If not, it's my turn.
A gun.
This is not something we should see.
I'm sorry.
I'm really sorry
to have kept you two waiting.
Butler Wang,
is the cargo okay?
No problem.
Not a single bottle broken.
Mr. William
is very satisfied.
He asked me to thank you two.
Please accept this.
Mr. William is so generous.
He is indeed a prominent figure
in Jiangcheng.
Alright.
Since the cargo is fine,
we won't bother you anymore.
Please wait.
It's not easy to escort the goods.
Mr. William
prepared two gifts for you to take back.
They are imported Cuban cigars.
If Mr. Shen remembers correctly,
these are Chief Xu's favorites.
That's very thoughtful.
But coincidentally,
these cigars
are stuck at customs.
You'll have to wait a bit.
Why don't you two stay a few more days?
I have no problem with that.
I've heard Jiangcheng
has lots of great food and fun.
Yes.
Tianbai,
what about you?
Then I’ll have to trouble you.
However...
Not at all.
I don't want to stay with him.
What do you mean?
I'm telling you,
I'll go wherever you go today.
What if you poison and kill me?
Suit yourself.
Do you think I really want to follow you?
Don't look back.
Someone is following us.
You caught that.
You never call me Tianbai.
Tianbai,
what about you?
Pretty smart.
On the left.
What do you mean?
Why are you walking so fast?
You won't talk, huh?
I can go wherever I want.
I'll just follow you.
The Duke of Zhou was named Ji Dan.
He was the fourth son of King Wen of Zhou,
and the younger brother of King Wu.
Because his fief was in Zhou,
he was appointed as the highest duke,
hence called the Duke of Zhou.
He twice aided King Wu in his campaign
to overthrow King Zhou.
[Jiangcheng Library]
After King Wu's death,
he acted as regent for King Cheng,
established rites and music,
and brought great order to the world.
He claimed that
he would wring his hair three times
during a bath
and spit out his food three times
during a meal.
all to rise and receive worthy men.
I didn't expect a gentleman
to come to a place like this.
This is a storytelling house.
Many women tell stories here.
Dignitaries love to come here
to appear cultured.
It's safer.
The Industrial and Commercial Bureau here
has long been controlled by foreigners.
They have always had conflicts
with the Chinese Chamber of Commerce.
Recently, the foreigners plan to
revise the regulations,
adding many new excuses to collect money.
The Chinese Chamber of Commerce
is against it
and have been protesting for a month.
Those atms are meant to suppress them.
But this matter can't be revealed.
Once it is exposed,
Jiangcheng will definitely be in chaos.
That's why William got the goods
from Ningcheng.
And hired two completely unrelated gangs
to escort them.
I didn't expect
that we two unlucky guys
would stumble upon his secret.
Maybe we will die in a foreign land.
They've been sending people to follow us.
Have they already found out?
Not necessarily.
It might just be
the government's procedure.
These officials are very cautious.
They usually take three to five days
to inspect the goods.
Before that, they naturally have someone
follow us.
William's attitude is still uncertain.
If we run away in a hurry,
it will only arouse his suspicion.
That's right.
As expected of Officer Shen,
you know these things
like the back of your hand.
Even if you joined the gang,
your time in the police force
wasn't in vain.
Instead of being sarcastic here,
you should figure out who is trying
to harm us.
What's your brilliant idea, Officer Shen?
If you hadn't gone crazy,
how could we have gotten into
such big trouble?
Is that so?
Why do I remember it was because
someone wanted to kill me?
Don't you want to kill me?
Of course I do.
Then why don't you do it?
Shen Tianbai.
Do you think I'm an idiot?
If I kill you,
how will I get out alone?
But,
once this is over,
I will still find a chance to kill you.
Likewise.
I've already tried to contact Uncle Zhong.
Let's wait a bit longer.
Until then,
let's wait and see.
There's a change of plan.
We leave tonight.
We can't take the train.
-We have to take the water route.
-Water route.
But I'm a little surprised.
I definitely can't escape alone,
but with your skills,
we have a 70 or 80% chance of escaping
in the middle of the night.
Why did you tell me?
Wouldn't it be perfect to let me die here?
If I left,
wouldn't you sell me out?
Bingo.
Good thing you made the right choice.
Mr. Shen, Mr. Lu,
Mr. William would like to
buy you two a drink tonight.